

Profile

Passionate Front-end developer with over 3 years of experience working with **Angular** to develop efficient code for products and businesses ranging from marketing websites to complex solutions and enterprise applications with a focus on fast, elegant, and accessible user experiences. An enthusiastic team player, problem solver, and deep creative thinker. This is my <u>portfolio</u>.

Employment History

Frontend Engineer, Origin Markets, London, UK

MARCH 2022 - PRESENT

• Working on a financial platform for issuer and dealer.

Angular Developer, Code & Care, Kharkiv, Ukraine

SEPTEMBER 2021 - JUNE 2022

• Transforming an old legacy desktop software for paper management into a web application using Angular.

Lead Frontend Developer, Renmoney, Lagos, Nigeria

MARCH 2020 - APRIL 2020

- Built a fully-fledged fintech loan web application that allows millions of users to have access to credit and also save their funds using Angular.
- Lead the frontend team.

Frontend Developer (Angular), Tr1pp, London, UK

JULY 2021 - NOVEMBER 2021

• Built and managed a large project management system used by government parastatals using Angular.

Wordpress Developer, NXTFactor, New York, USA

OCTOBER 2019 - JUNE 2021

 Built numerous beautiful websites with WordPress using page builders like Elementor.

WordPress Developer, Midland Digital Solutions, Lagos, Nigeria.

AUGUST 2020 - DECEMBER 2020

 Built numerous beautiful websites with WordPress using page builders like Elementor.

Frontend Developer (Angular), Terragon Group, Lagos, Nigeria

JUNE 2019 - FEBRUARY 2020

- Built and managed a survey web application platform for creating survey and data collections for our clients using Angular.
- Collaborated with internal teams and vendors to fix and improve product quality.

Math Tutor, Phoebestar Royalty Schools, Osogbo, Nigeria

OCTOBER 2014 - JULY 2018

• Taught Mathematics and Further Mathematics.

Details

Room C, 111 Holly Court,,
John Harrison Way,, Greenwich,
London.
Lagos, SE10 0BL.
United Kingdom

+447733821980

lawaldare@gmail.com

Links

LinkedIn

Github

Twitter

Portfolio

Skills

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Angular

Wordpress

Typescript

SCSS

Hobbies

Watching Movies, Coding

Languages

English Language

Education

Bachelor degrees, University of Ilorin, Ilorin, Nigeria

DECEMBER 2009 - JULY 2012

Certifications

Google Africa Developer Training Program, Google

FEBRUARY 2021